Guide to the Stanford University, Planning Office, Records SC0486
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-1990-052
  - Program for mineral engineering at Stanford, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Peter Coutts hill, housing analysis, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Peter Coutts hill, floor plans by Fisher-Friedman of other cluster housing, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Peter Coutts hill, preliminary design, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - SLAC, draft environmental assessment, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Old Firehouse, historic structures report, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Inner Quad renovation, 1982-83 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Inner Quad renovation, 1983-85 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Palo Alto - history (assorted brochures, publications), 1953-58 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Memorial Church roof, newspaper article on, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Map - master plan of land use, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Project flow chart (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - ITEK photographs - correspondence, memo, 1972-73 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Dorm study - plot plan (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Historical timeline re campus development, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Faculty facilities - children's play area, 1969-71 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Historical - Olmsted sesquicentennial, January 1972 - May 1973 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Historical - Olmsted sesquicentennial, June 1973 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Historical - Olmsted Brothers, 1944-72 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Historical - Olmsted letters, May 1888 - August 1890 (copies) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Historical - Olmsted preliminary report [typescript copy], 1914 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Historical - Olmsted - typescript copies of documents (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Plan [drawing] for proposed intersection of Palm and Campus Drives, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Campus maps (also includes shopping center and Pine Hill No. 2), 1960-64 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Faculty/staff housing - minutes, memos, maps, 1967, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Dorm booklets (Stern 1961, Cedro 1960) (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Mineral sciences at Stanford (academic booklet) (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Fraternities at Stanford (2 editions) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Planning Office make-up [assorted maps and plans re student housing] (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Reguest for addition of lands to the academic reserve, Dept. of Biological Sciences, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Residence and commute patterns [of] employees, Stanford Industrial Park, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Report to the Board of Trustees, 1954 [general info on the University] (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Study of and proposal for the use of a portion of the lands of LSJU, Peninsula Pacific Construction Co., 1955 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Comparison of housing for married students at various universities (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous items (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Tempko, Allan - articles on S.F. and bay area architecture (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Water resources, 1960-63 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - S.U. Medical Center master plan, 1979, site and floor plans, 1977, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Livingston & Blayney, S.U. Land Use Policy/Plan, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Skidmore, Owings & Merrill, report on resident development area 6 of S.U. lands, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Interim space facilities, report, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Assorted land use maps, 1950-66 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Student papers: Civil Engineering projects re traffic, 1957-58 RESTRICTED (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Student papers: Campus Drive traffice, 1959 RESTRICTED (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Student papers: parking; Memorial Arch - 1959 RESTRICTED (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Student papers: traffic conditions in Pine Hill 2, 1964 RESTRICTED (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Student papers: traffic, 1959 RESTRICTED (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Additional Material, Accessions ARCH-1990-086, 1993-006, and 1997-009
  - Schroder, Dirk. Memoranda regarding trees and landscaping on campus, 1962-1967. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Olmsted vs. Shepley, Rutan & Coolidge - undated, unsigned typescript, about which architect was responsible for what aspects of the university's design, 3 pp. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Planning Report: Inspection of Several College Campuses, September, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Serra Mall proposal, Sebastian & Associates, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-1995-174
  - Files kept by Harry Sanders
    - Study of Art Department needs, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - White Plaza, student paper by Lisa Bennett, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - List of memorial plaques on campus, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Handbook of Stanford history, rought draft (S.U. Historical Society project) (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Contributions by landscape architects to recent S. U. campus development (map and list), 1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Olmsted correspondence (photocopies) (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Background material (H. Sanders' notebook): buildings (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Background material (H. Sanders' notebook): statistics, housing (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Background material (H. Sanders' notebook): land development (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Background material (H. Sanders' notebook): cost info, general info (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Planning office manual (notebook) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Planning Office Reports
    - Palo Alto-Menlo Park Area Transportation Project, Final Report, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Development of Circulation and Parking for the Academic Campus of Stanford University, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Master Plan, Stanford University Medical Center, Clinical Facilities, Phase I, Step I, (2 copies), 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Land Use Plan, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Stanford University Sand Hill Road Projects, (2 copies), 1995 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Project Management at Stanford University; a Report to the Board of Trustees, February, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - The Cost of Building at Stanford University; a Report to the Board of Trustees, February, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Planning Publications of other institutions
    - Campus Planning 1967, Society for College and University Planning (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Educational Facilities Laboratories, case study on modernization (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Designs for Learning.. .architectural criteria for college facilities planned to utilize instructional aids and media, Vol. I; report of a research project conducted by the School of Architecture, RPI (includes photographs) (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Washington University, brochure on development, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - California Monthly, special architectural issue, April 1954 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Tulane University Medical Center Master Plan, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Design Study Duke University, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Housing and the Future of Cities in the San Francisco Bay Area by Catherine Bauer Wurster, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Domestic architecture in Bay Area, several articles (I.J. Quillen house on Stanford campus is mentioned in one) (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Stanford University Medical Center, Site and Floor Plans, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Stanford University Medical Center, Site and Floor Plans, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-1996-176
  - The Architects Collaborative Inc. Near West Campus Redevelopment Project: Conceptial Regional Designs; Interim Planning Report. November 1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Skidmore Owings and Merrill. Master Plan for Stanford Lands 1953. Report to the Board of Trustees; and Supplement No. 1 Economic Factors of the Master Plan (2 cc) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Jasper Ridge at Stanford University; A wilderness experimental area for long-range studies in population biology. [Stanford University, n.d.] (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The Architects Collaborative Inc. Near West Campus Redevelopment Project: Conceptial Regional Designs; Supplementary Planning Report. November 1985 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-1998-054
  - Regional Planning of the Stanford Campus, September 11, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Stanford University Landscape Design Guidelines, March 1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Region Plan: Near East, Frost and Serra, May 1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Zebroski, Ortha. Palm Drive Entryway Area Plan, March 31, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-1999-151
  - Oversize reports and sketches (Box 1 os)
    - Polshek & Partners, Architects. "Iris & B. Gerald Cantor Center for the Visual Arts: Precedents and Inpiration." Undated. Contains color xerox photos and drawings, as well as text.
    - Pei Cobb Freed & Partners, Architects. "[SEQ] Program Site Visits 1 Dec 94; 8 Dec 94." Contains color xerox photos and notes re various elements of existing compus architecture/facilities, etc.
    - Pei Cobb Freed & Partners, Architects. Sketch of SEQ, focusing on electrical engineering building, Sept. 14, 1995
    - [Pei Cobb Freed & Partners, Architects]. Enlarged color xeroxes of sketches of SEQ buildings
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2000-013
  - Encina Hall East Wing historical analysis with 49 photographs, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Encina East Wing - 8mm video tape (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Gladding, McBean - drawings of tile profiles, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Hoover Tower repair proposal by Architectural Resources Group, with photographs (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Main Quad mortar analysis (with sample of mortar), 1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous: notes on several campus buildings; holiday card from Architectural Resources Group (includes image of Hanna House), 1999 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2000-104
  - San Mateo County Planning Dept. Stanford Lands Study. A Review of Plans for the Future Development of the Lands of Stanford University Lying within San Mateo County. January 1968 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Study for the Development of the Stanford Campus Area. 1950 [A revision of the 1947 plan prepared for Lewis Mumford; with illustrations] (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Hutchison, E. Elmore. Report on Land Use Survey of Stanford University Properties San Mateo and Santa Clara Counties, California. June 1951 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Skidmore, Owings & Merrill. Master Plan for Stanford Lands 1953. Supplement 1: Economic Factors of the Master Plan [2 different copies] (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Skidmore, Owings & Merrill. Master Plan for Stanford Lands 1953. Report to the Board of Trustees [2 copies in binders] (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Livingston and Blayney. Stanford University Land Use Policy/Plan 1971. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Wilsey, Ham & Blair. Improvement Study of San Francisquito Creek San Mateo and Santa Clara Counties, California. 1964 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Two campus maps, ca. 1970, with markings on residential areas (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2001-203
  - Planning by Area - Quad 4 (Science), 1981-83 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - Near West Campus - Phase II, 1986-87 [NWC Design, Review of Alternatives, Plan Scope and Specificity, Project Team, NWC Admin, Planning Group] (Box 1, Folder 3-6)
  - Near West Campus - miscellaneous items (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - SEQ (Science and Engineering Quad) - booklets, 1995-96 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - SEQ roof tile color - photos and correspondence, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - SEQ miscellaneous sketches (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - RRL (Ronald Reagan Library) Committee, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - RRL - Campus Report articles 1983 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - RRL - correspondence, 1981-83 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - RRL - site analysis (1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 2-3)
  - RRL - Chronology of siting process (Box 2, Folder 4-5)
  - Area Plan Proposed Presidential Library - draft, March 1987 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Campus Street Lighting, report 1953 with photographs and plans (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Hoover, Abigail. Internship report, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Inner Quad Courtyard - assorted sources, 1982-83 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Mumford, Lewis - copies of correspondence and reports, 1947-50 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Olmsted, Frederick Law - miscellaneous items pertaining to FLO Birthday Celebration on campus, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Proposed Solution to the Stanford Parking Problem - students' report, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Report on Foothills Region Access and Parking Issues, Public Affairs Council Report, April 20, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Standards for campus construction materials, equipment, and procedures, 1963-76 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Stanford University Land Use Policy/Plan- Campus Report Supplement, March 29, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - SEQ - two sketches (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - SEQ - Maya Lin sketches, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2002-033
  - Campus Plan for the Second Century, 1991 Jun (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Toyon Hall Seismic Evaluation Report, Rutherford & Chekene, 1999 Feb (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Toyon Exterior Report, color xerox of photos, 1999 Apr 15 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Toyon Interior Report, color xerox of photos, 1999 Apr 15 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Toyon Hall, formulation scope check, Cody Anderson Wasney architects, 2000 Sep 27 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - arcCA 2002 - includes note of SU building receiving award (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2002-292
  - The 1975 Program For Main Library Development (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Specifications for Terman Engineering Center (Harry Weese & Associates, architects), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Campus Center Public Space On-Site Workshops, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Memo re naming 579 Alvarado as Van Patten House, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2004-292
  - The 1975 Program For Main Library Development (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Specifications for Terman Engineering Center (Harry Weese & Associates, architects), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Campus Center Public Space On-Site Workshops, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Memo re naming 579 Alvarado as Van Patten House, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2005-041
  - Annexation (Stanford Lands to Palo Alto), Miscellaneous Projects (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Carpenter Parking Study 1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Carpenter - Parking Task Force 1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Church, Thomas (architect) clippings, reports, etc. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Heritage Trees (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Historical: Architectural Planning for Stanford May 1947- (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Historical: Architectural & Historical Survey of Stanford Univ. Buildings 1949 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Historical Architecture, Stanford - Opinions May 1947- (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Historical: Campus Planning - Harry Sanders 1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Historical: Crothers, George E. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Historical: Historical Buildings and Landmarks 1975 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Historical: Historical Buildings and Landmarks and Historic Preservation 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Historical: Historical Surveys (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Historical: Lewis Mumford Correspondence and Report (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Historical: Stanford Architecture 1884- (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Historical, etc - Stanford (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Historical Preservation: National Register Listing (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Land Development: General Annexation (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Land Development 1952-1954 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Landscaping: Campus, Inner Quad 1948- (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Landscaping: Campus Jan. 1951- June 1960 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Landscaping: Campus May 1961- Aug. 1966 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Landscaping: Campus Sept. 1967-Apr. 1972 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Landscaping: Campus 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Landscaping: Land Development June 1951- Nov. 1959 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Landscaping: Land Development Jan.1960- (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Maps: Land Use - General 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Master Plan: Stanford Land Use and Map Permit (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Master Plan Review: Livingston and Blayney Consultants - Draft Copy of Final Report December 1970 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - McCullough Renovation Project, Progress Report May 1998 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Plans and Builds 1949 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Plans and Builds 1976 Library Addition (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Sand Hill Road Projects (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - SS Cornerstone Week (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Stanford Architecture: Historical (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Stanford Photos: Historical (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Street Trees: Landscaping - General (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Stanford SEQ Project Swinerton & Walberg Monthly Report July 1997 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Stanford SEQ Project Swinerton & Walberg Monthly Report Nov. 1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Stanford SEQ Project Swinerton & Walberg Monthly Report Dec. 1998 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2005-116
  - Thornton Center - 1.1 General - 1991 - 1.0 Planning and Programming (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Thornton Center - 1.2 General - 1992 - 1.0 Planning and Programming (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Thornton Center - 2.1 General - 1992 - 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Thornton Center - 2.2 General - 1993 - 2.0 Design and Documenation (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Thornton Center - 3.1 General - 3.0 Construction and Occupancy (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Thornton Center - 4.1 General - 4.0 Graphics and Materials (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Landscape Conversions (GPI) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Interim Chemical Storage Facility (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Archaeology Alert Signal Facility (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Building 01-070 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ME Seismic Surge Building 02-540 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - MC/CE Buiding 02-520/542 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Memorial Auditorium (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Building 01-001 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Frost Amphitheater (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Herrin Lab (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Cobb Track Bleachers (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Memorial Church (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Building 01-001 Seismic (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Building 02-610 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Building 02-530 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Building 01-080 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Humanities Annex (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Athletics Quad Connective Elements (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Campus Edges (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Serra Street Storm Drain (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Mudd Chemistry Liquid Nitrogen Tank (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Museum Site Clearance (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Medical School Lab Surge (MSLS/MRS) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Toxic Gas Storage Facility (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Medical School Lab Surge (MSLS/MRS) (Box 2, Folder 2-4)
  - Medical School Lab Surge (MSLS/MRS) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Medical School Lab Surge (MSLS/MRS) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Near West Campus Implementation (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Office of Development Trailer (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Palm Drive (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Palm Drive Entryway (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Physics Tank Modifications 6/91 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Psychiatric Center Clinic Building (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Psychiatric Center Clinic Building (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Psychiatric Center Clinic Building (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Psychiatric Center Clinic Building (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Psychiatric Center Clinic Building (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Psychiatric Center Clinic Building (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Psychiatric Center Clinic Building (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Quad Portals (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Parking Structure III - Material samples (Box 3)
  - Parking Structure III (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Parking Structure III (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Parking Structure III (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Parking Structure III (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Sand Hill Road Extension 1978-1986 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Sand Hill Road Extension 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Sand Hill Road Extension 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Slavianskii Dom (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Space Study, GCRS/Internal Audit (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Stern Hall (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - SUC/FPP Clinical Facility - 900 Blake Wilbur Drive (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - SUMC Fairchild Building Exterior Modification (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Widening of Welch at Pasteur (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Wilbur Hall Renovations (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Wilbur Modular Awnings (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Housing Inventory (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Planning Office Goals project 1990 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Santa Clara Valley AIA meeting 1993 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - PO Strategic Plan 1991-92 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Health and Safety (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Medical Center LRFPG (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - VTSS program - Building 01-370 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - VTSS program - Building 01-370 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Operations Council [committees, Univ. Admin.] 1989-92 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Welch Crossing LPCH 1993-94 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Green Earth Sciences Building 1988 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Green Earth Sciences Building 1988 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Green Earth Sciences Building 1989 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Green Earth Sciences Building 1988 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Green Earth Sciences Building 1990 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Hass Center 1991-93 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Hass Center 1991 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Hill Houses Demolition 1991-94 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Kimball Hall 1989-90 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Kimball Hall 1988-91 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Kimball Hall 1979, 1990-91 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Kimball Hall (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Lathrop Carriage House Demolition 1992 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Memorial Church Earthquake Projects 1991 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Knoll Student Housing (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Knoll Student Housing (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Knoll Student Housing (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Auxiliary Library II (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - APC-FAT [Facilities Action Team] Committee 1990 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - APC-FAT Committee 1990 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Cost and Process Study 1991 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Architectural Agreement 1993 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Financial Operating Group 1993 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Repositioning and Budget Issues 1992 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - SCRL Process 1991 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Humanities Annex 11-105 exterior (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Psychiatry Sign (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - 2725 Sand Hill Road (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - English Building -1-060 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - FPP Clinical Building (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Gilbert Biological Sciences (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Red Barn 1982 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Red Barn Site Improvements 1986 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Student Barn 1987 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - DC Powers Lab site 1985 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Residential GPI 1984 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Main Quad Improvements 1978 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Outdoor Furniture 1984 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Quad Reconstruction brochure (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Quad Front Restoration 1985 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Knoll - A/C vs. Awnings (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Memorial Auditorium - Personnel door (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Forsythe Equipment/Yard (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Forsythe Hall - antennae (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Sunken Diamond Concession Stand 1991 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Ronald McDonald House expansion 89-91 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Arcade Shoring Artwork - Student Project 1990-91 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Building 610 Portal 1989 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Charter Psychiatric Center drawing 1989 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Green Library Identification Sign 1990 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Hoover House 1987 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Maples Pavilion Expansion 1989 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Mariposa House Feasibility Study 1989-90 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - SITN new facility siting 1990 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Visitors Center 1990 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Woodworth House 545 Forest Ave PA 1990 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Bookstore Remodel 1989 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Campus Drive West 1989 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Cooling Tower #4 1990 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Ford Center Fieldhouse (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Information Sciences 1990 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Old Pavilion Renovation 1989 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Post Office 1987 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Mayfield School site 1981 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Kingscote 1981 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Gas Receiving Station 1988 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Rural Lane 1982-86 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Ryan Court 1989 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Westin Hotel Site 1991 (Box 6, Folder 23)